Register of the Robert Alfred Theobald papers, 1908-1959
Hoover Institution Archives
- Naval Career Office File, 1908-1949 (Boxes 10-13)
  - Operations plans and orders, 1942
    - Comtaskforce 8
      - No. 11-42, undated
      - No. 12-42, October 12
      - No. 13-42, October 12
      - No. 14-42, November 19
      - No. 15-42, December 2
      - No. 16-42, December 26
    - Comtaskgroup 8.1 (Air Group, Eleventh Air Force)
      - No. 1-42, May 28
      - No. 2-42, June 9
      - Field Orders No. 1, June 24
      - Field Orders No. 2, June 25
      - Field Orders No. 3, July 16
      - Field Orders No. 4, August 23
    - Comtaskunit 8.1.1 (Air Striking Unit, Eleventh Air Force)
      - Field Orders No. 4, June 25
      - Field Orders No. 5, July 16
      - Field Orders No. 6, August 3
      - Field Orders No. 7, August 23
      - Field Orders No. 8, November 1
    - Comtaskunit 8.1.2 (Air Search Unit, Eleventh Air Force), No. 3-42, June 29
    - Comtaskgroup 8.2 (Surface Search Group), No. 1-42, May 28
    - Comtaskgroup 8.3 (Air Striking Group, Eleventh Air Force)
      - Field Orders No. 1, May 28
      - Field Orders No. 2, June 1
      - Field Orders No. 3, June 11
    - Comtaskgroup 8.5 (Submarines)
      - No. 1-42, June 29
      - No. 4-42, July 5
      - No. 2-42, August 11
      - No. 3-42, November 26
    - Compatwing 4
      - Standard Communications Plan (Box 13)
      - Operations Schedule for Project Queen, August 2
      - Search Plan Dog, August 17
      - Operations Schedule for Project King
    - Eleventh Air Force
      - Plan of Operations, Project Queen
      - Plan of Operations, Project King
    - Comalsec, No. 1-42, July 16
    - U.S.S. Nashville (flagship of Task Force 8), Outline of Plan for Handling Flare Attack, August 25
    - Directive for Provision of Aircraft Support to Ships at Sea
  - Service lists, 1942-1944
  - War estimates, 1940-1943
- Subject File, 1951-1957 (Box 13)
  Articles and letters, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Marshall, George C., 1951 March
    The Tragedy of George Marshall by Walter Trohan, The American Mercury.
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1953
  - Theobald, Rear Admiral Robert A., 1957
    Letters of condolence on the occasion of Admiral Theobald's death and memorial service program.
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, undated
    Foreword to The Soviet Impact on Society by Dr. Dagobert D. Runes.
- Miscellany, 1944-1951 (Box 13)
  - Commencement programs
- Declassified U.S. Government Records, 1942-1943 (Box 13)
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder chronologically by date of creation.
  - 2015 May release of records, 1942-1943
    Operations plans, war diaries, orders, correspondence, and dispatches.
  - 2016 February release of records, 1942
    Appendices to Operation Plans and Communication Plans. See also: Naval Career Office File.